<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Privacy Discussions in Toronto</title>
    <link>https://privacytoronto.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Privacy Discussions in Toronto</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 24 May 2017 23:10:05 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://privacytoronto.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Feedback - Privacy 101: An Open Discussion</title>
      <link>https://privacytoronto.github.io/blog/2017/05/feedback---privacy-101-an-open-discussion/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 May 2017 23:10:05 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://privacytoronto.github.io/blog/2017/05/feedback---privacy-101-an-open-discussion/</guid>
      <description>Our first event took place the 16th of May, and it was amazing ! Here is a short summary of our discussions that day.
Threat Models When we consider physical security, we are constantly developing models in order to be secure in our daily life : don&amp;rsquo;t drive when you are drunk, be careful when going in certain areas&amp;hellip; These models are really personals, each one of us develop a different threat model depending on where we live, what activities we have, who we are (in terms of race, gender, sexual orientation&amp;hellip;) etc.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Privacy 101: An Open Discussion - 16th of May 2017</title>
      <link>https://privacytoronto.github.io/events/2017/05/privacy-101-an-open-discussion---16th-of-may-2017/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 May 2017 18:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://privacytoronto.github.io/events/2017/05/privacy-101-an-open-discussion---16th-of-may-2017/</guid>
      <description>The first Privacy Discussion will be held the 16th of May 2017 at the 519 Community Center from 6pm to 8pm. We&amp;rsquo;ll combine a brief talk and a workshop, and leave time for a Q&amp;amp;A/extended discussion.
Program  Introduction What Are Your Concerns? A Threat Modeling Introduction (10 minutes) Workshop : Strategies Of Resistance (45 minutes) Break (10 minutes) Talk : Chat Apps / Secure Passwords Open Discussion : Q&amp;amp;A with facilitators and attendees  What you should bring  Your curiosity Your motivation Something to take notes Any device you are comfortable with (optional)  Before coming to the event, please take some time to read the Code Of Conduct</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Protect Your Privacy at a Protest</title>
      <link>https://privacytoronto.github.io/blog/2017/05/how-to-protect-your-privacy-at-a-protest/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 May 2017 23:46:16 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://privacytoronto.github.io/blog/2017/05/how-to-protect-your-privacy-at-a-protest/</guid>
      <description>The Intercept has published a good video explaining how to protect your safety during protests (with Matt Mitchell and Micah Lee) :
  See the full article here</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Code Of Conduct</title>
      <link>https://privacytoronto.github.io/codeofconduct/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Apr 2017 00:02:28 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://privacytoronto.github.io/codeofconduct/</guid>
      <description>Code of Conduct Privacy Toronto is dedicated to providing a harassment-free environment for everyone, regardless of gender, sexual orientation, ability, physical appearance, body size, age, race, religion, immigration status, or any other grounds. We do not tolerate harassment of anyone in any form.
Be kind to others. Do not insult or put down other attendees. Behave humanly. Harassment and bigoted or exclusionary comments are not tolerated, and individuals violating these rules may be asked to leave our events at the sole discretion of the event organizers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Resources</title>
      <link>https://privacytoronto.github.io/resources/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Apr 2017 23:35:11 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://privacytoronto.github.io/resources/</guid>
      <description>Here is a non-exhaustive list of resources on privacy and security:
 A DIY Guide to Feminist Cybersecurity breaks down different terms and topics and explains privacy considerations in an accessible format. Topics range from social media to phones to anonymous web browsing, and include links to many other resources. It&amp;rsquo;s a great read.
 EFF Surveillance Self-Defense Guide is an extensive yet (fairly) easy-to-read collection of tutorials and guides for a variety of situations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About Us</title>
      <link>https://privacytoronto.github.io/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Apr 2017 23:29:20 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://privacytoronto.github.io/about/</guid>
      <description>Privacy Discussions in Toronto started with the desire to have accessible, friendly, and practical conversations about digital privacy, and to encourage those conversations outside of the typical tech sphere. It&amp;rsquo;s easy for tech talks to become intimidating or inaccessible, but our goal is to connect people who are interested in digital privacy issues and to provide a space to discuss, learn, and demystify.
Tech spaces can also look pretty homogenous, and we want to disrupt that.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Home</title>
      <link>https://privacytoronto.github.io/home/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Apr 2017 23:29:20 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://privacytoronto.github.io/home/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to Privacy Discussions in Toronto! We are a group of people who aim to increase global awareness and knowledge about privacy and security, starting in our own communities. Our focus is digital privacy, and in particular, making conversation about digital spaces accessible and uncomplicated.
We organize events in Toronto about privacy&amp;ndash;check out our next event. We also welcome suggestions, contributors, and anyone who wants to get involved or host their own Privacy Discussions.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>